If you've used Great Plains GP for 20
years, GP seems simple. But then you use
Business Central, it's just so much
easier, so much more intuitive. It does
things automatically that you used to
have to press buttons to make the system
do.
Not long after we launched the business,
we found the BC talent program and
that's been a game [music] changer. I
joined the cross skills program because
I knew that I had to be intentional with
my time. Carving out intentional [music]
time that will be dedicated to skilling
myself to become a weapon for my clients
was priority. I think the biggest
[music]
drive for me was the size of the class
and knowing that there would be
different mediums and being a small
boutique firm, you know, Chris and I
really [music] have appreciated the
people that we met there and that we've
leaned on. Quite frankly, it's been
hugely beneficial for us.
There is no chance that without cross
skills and BC talent program that we
would have achieved certification or
gained the confidence to sit in front of
prospects and customers without [music]
this program.
>> The biggest value I got out of the BC
talent program was the confidence that I
had walking into conversations knowing
that I can successfully move them from
GP to BC [music] in the least risky,
least disruptive way.
>> We know exactly how we're going to train
up our future team members. When our
future team members come on, they're
going into [music] the BC talent
program.